re247365.com 2014-12-22

# RE 24/7/365

## Privacy Policy

### Statement of Privacy

Thank you for visiting our web site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. This document describes how we use personal information collected on this site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described below. These practices may be changed but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a non-retroactive, going forward basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

### Collection of Information

Your online privacy is important to us, and we respect the privacy of your personal information which you are entrusting to us. We will use the information you provide only for the purpose(s) intended. This means: we will NOT sell, trade, rent or distribute your personal information to other third parties, for any reason, without your consent. 

### Links To Other Web Sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites ("Links") which are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave our web site. RE is not responsible for the content of the other web sites or the privacy and condition of use practices and policies employed by their site(s). Thus, RE does not endorse or make any representations about linked sites, or any information, software or other products or materials found therein, or any results that may be obtained from using the data on these sites. If you decide to access any of the third party web sites linked from our web site, you do this entirely at your own risk. 

### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technologies are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 

### Utilization Tracking

RE tracks information related to overall user traffic patterns throughout our site in order to make decisions regarding content and services. 

### Log Files

Traffic pattern tracking and monitoring is used on our site for maintenance purposes. Site related performance issues are often diagnosed and tested using a user's personal information. 

### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information provided to these agencies or companies is not for marketing purposes. 

### Commitment To Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have entered into a confidentiality agreement) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow users the option to opt out of further mailings. 

### Contact Information

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact RE Home Base at 612-888-6942.
